feel through pretty sure that's mason he says no it isn't the code 80%
on the drums keeping perfect time then starts another pointless argument on
life technically actually historically speaking brother just want to expose the
things first of all same man is allowing doxing of my thing by this um like this
visage loser who's claiming some kind of gang affiliation called I guess he was
Tell me if you guys can tell me who he was in that candle kickers, but he says he's in the psyche psychos
He's sending me text messages. He's using the exact same picture that it's using but I just want to expose this one
This is beat us chat. I'll expose this on beat us chat
And here's how they talk and beat us chat who owns the building where Norman Bates lives. Well, I'll just make sure I don't
It's gonna expose and I'll tell you who's saying this and these are people you should watch out for because they're people that were
apparently wanting real life to go in and
I guess, you know ruining people's lives. So I'll share this once you here we go
My background. Okay. Here we go. Here's the text or not the text it was on I guess when the text is to me
I get this background on the background is not coming off
weird, okay
Okay, I'll coming up. Okay. Well, anyway, I try my best to show you
Okay, so we have Jenny girl Jen Jen, okay?
Someone named Jenny girl Jen Jen. She looks like some old hag
Basically, she's always in beatus chat. Okay, so Jenny girl Jen Jen who owns the building where Norman Bates lives
This is in beatus chat by the way
Then I am person stop it with the AI shit. This is beatus chat. So if they don't like I mean, I don't have to watch it
I mean, it's like but I'll stop it with the okay person's not telling and then I'll see then I'm person says oh
His family owns it
Well, you know, you know, you know when someone's in a family, I'm in the family too. Okay, so
You can say I own it. Okay. Let's go. Let's we can go on boycott AI person. Okay
Let's see. What does it say next? It says Christine
Psych he said a neighbor did a background check on him a while ago
He well, they just looked up the building on online. Okay, just like, you know, Alex did okay
He has him giving off creepo vibes, he-man-she-ra.
Even having space between living houses sounds,
sound travels, and it's annoying to most.
Oh yeah, it must have been annoying last night
when they called the police when I was screaming,
trying to talk over summer,
which I was not able to do
because she's just filibusters, right?
Then, and then person keeps going,
stop it with the AI, then Jenny girl says,
then they may be forced to do something.
Yeah, I may be forced to
Fucking put a pie in your face Jenny girl Jen Jen. What is it your fucking business you cunt?
I am person AI works on prior data. Not back. Oh cares person. You're such a loser and then
Jenny girl his family. I mean, yeah, my family may be forced to sue some of these people actually
You know slandering and fucking in things that are none of their business. I mean, it's like really
I'm going to show you, these people want me to start looking into their living situation
and let's look into who owns their houses and stuff like that.
Why shouldn't we do that?
I mean, they're so comfortable to talk about me.
I mean, it's so, so crazy.
And I'm actually on camera.
Oh, my house is dirty.
I'm on the same ends.
None of these people are on camera.
No, I'm on camera.
And they're saying, oh, all this shit about me.
So stupid.
And I'll go over the summer stuff again.
Summer, you know, who's supposed to be a friend
and stuff like that.
All of a sudden, didn't want me to talk last night.
Yeah, so, yeah.
No, you know, it's bad getting to that point.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
You know you shouldn't really fuck with people that actually have you know a family of attorneys and stuff like that
But anyway, I digress anyway
Yeah, summer I went over the messages last night. She asked me for help with something
You know and then so I said summer can I have five minutes of your time?
I want to ask you about something because I know she had been doxxed and stuff and I just wanted to get her advice about her
severe doxxes and stuff
She ignored ignored
Know I know it is it's so wrong. It's so wrong and it's it's it's I think it's illegal. I mean, but yeah
Yeah, yeah, so I'm gonna mod you soon. I can't I'm just like I'm looking for my vape this morning
Last night I did a reading for somebody. It was awesome and they sent me like a beautiful dinner
It was like just the awesome night
The police came and then they're like they're like turn down your music and I was like it was 1030 at night and I said
Okay. Okay. And they're like, they're like, well, you have neighbors think about your neighbors and I'm like, well, my neighbors
Are rude to me. I don't really give a fuck, you know, but anyway
At least in like, I guess like you're gonna throw a fucking doorbell through my window again, right?
Anyhow, I don't know. It's just like people all on other people's business and they don't like people in theirs
I mean, that's why if I do anything, I think I have a drink
My videos get hundreds of views. Oh, you don't all you do is stream beta and stupid AI
I'm this stage this stage. Here's a here's a text message from this stage
This morning, I know it's him because he's using the same groovy Jimmy photos that only RG and him use, you know
And he's talking like I'm bothering beta listen to this listen to this how obsessed this and I GG ER is with her
He says, and I'm not being racial.
I'm just, you know, if, whatever.
Here we go.
Yeah, I love you sweetheart.
Okay, one second.
So it says.
Okay, there's a bunch of disgusting pictures of vaginas and stuff.
It says, you better leave Bida alone, or I and the other rabbis will have Hashem bring
a Shoah down on your family for the next century.
Your tukus is Mossad's.
Now stop the music or get the business Busy Boy.
Okay, what is that?
I don't know what that means, but it's kind of unusual and there's disgusting pictures
of somebody's butthole.
If I get bish, okay, here I'll read these ones.
It says, AI is saying stop being a desperate
F-A-G seeking validation online like a bish.
And then it's like, I guess it's Groovy Jimmy's family.
Cause it's like, I don't know.
I don't know if you know who these people are, I'm not sure.
It looks like somebody in groupie Jimmy, Lucky Luciano.
I don't know who that person is.
And it says, stop snitching you effing F-A-G.
You better not. You ain't going anywhere but an AIDS clinic. F-U bitch.
You're threatened to K-I-L-L Alex.
Show that to the police. Stop sexually harassing...
And I showed all these to the police, by the way.
Stop sexually harassing beta and minors.
Show that to the police, you rapist freak.
You lose...
n-i-g-g-e-r sucker. You're texting yourself fake messages. You made these text-down numbers. I'm reporting you to the SCPA.
You don't deserve cats. You choke cats like n-i-g-g-e-r dick. You're a freak. I'm reporting you
to the police. Your pdf, your midget a's, n-i-g-g-e-r, mud-borne, f-a-g.
You're already in hell. Shout out to Jody. Jody sucks a duck for two dollars.
that's over and over again retire to the fire fag you're a monster and a rapist you act like a
psychic to lure kids to your channel you used to like russian kid videos on tiktok we didn't
forget back all fake threats if you snitch i'ma fuck you with a lawnmower just kidding alex is
gonna kill you and get off your dad is sucking bald nigger monkey dick in hell kennel kickers
is dismantled we're now psyches psychos your dad is sucking bald
N-I-G-G-E-R monkey dick in hell over and over.
Eight no 401k for evil.
You act like a psychic to lure kids to your channel.
You're fucking cats hate you.
I was talking to your mom too.
You're a spooky fag, unblock my stream yards.
Stop reading my text, F-A-G-G-E-T bitch.
Don't show my pics bitch.
You don't have permission to show any pics I sent you.
I'll report you F-A-G-G-O-T.
N-I-G-G-E-R, S-U-C-K-E-R, I'll make SIG rape you.
to change his pic or else don't show this message.
You effing bitch told you SIG is going to R-A-P-E-U
F-A-G-G-O-T bitch.
Okay, so those are the texts I'm getting.
That's just one.
I mean, it's like I have so many, so many, so many, so many.
I was, I got hundreds of them.
So yeah, so that's the kind of people I guess around here.
There are good people. Thank God, like you guys, but some of these people are really sick, you know
So I just wanted to expose that a little bit
You know, I was also exposed to get in the summer messages where I was very nice to summer and asked her things here
She goes as soon as you hear something from him, let me know so I can shut this rumor down because it's ridiculous
It's getting out of hand
Then I told her to come to my new channel. I said love you. Hope you're not upset with me over some dumb shit
Like everyone else is I was under some very nice things to say by dinner show yesterday. This one
I was friends with her. Thanks for sticking up for her. I hope you at least talk to me personally about things not just ghosts me
Have a good day. I'm not ignoring you. I'm just at work right now. I got a broken. Well fractured ankle
So let me get home and I'll hit you up tonight and she never did okay. I said, thank you
I do understand if you don't come because Paige is being harassed for supporting me
And then I had a fun night on a panel.
I had the best time goofing off, bullshitting last night,
kind of like old times, I needed that.
Hope you can make a panel soon.
I streamed from, and I gave my channel when I was streaming.
And I hope I'll be on shortly if you're around.
And then I said, Vitas on Samans,
whining about us, sounds like you had my back, thank you.
And I said, I love you.
And I said, I didn't type QT, I just said it for some reason.
I said, don't listen to those fair,
oh, here we are, here comes the text now.
Here we come with the text guys.
It says you're getting raped by Jewish AIDS-filled rabbis in hell over and over again, okay?
So that's what it says, and it says F-A-G-G-O-T, F-A-G-G-O-T. Brandon owns you.
You suck, N-I-G-G-E-R-D-S-E-K-F-A-G.
Stop sexually harassing Bita, and I'm gonna drop a Jewish nuke on you. The Jewish demons will kill you.
You're a
I'll reach hard PDF. You live in a tin can and suck off AIDS ridden juice. The soul harvest is coming
You'll perish in the Jewish fire over and over and over again
You're aren't allowed to go live dad sucker. You're a PDF. You have super AIDS FAG
Your dad is a semen demon sucking dick in hell get off panel monkey boy. You suck and IGG yours off FAG
I'm gonna give that dyke
whore AIDS and Chevy lawnmower for ass
INX is gonna get
Super AIDS from NIGG ERS. She's gonna get a Pogo stick of her D. Y. K. E. at
INX is gonna gamble as a PDF. Brandon owns your NIGG ERS. Let me see. Don't show my messages or
say them F-A-G. Don't show that dyke my messages boy. F-A-G-G-O-T several times over. Don't send
my messages. Recharge. You're getting... I mean, if you don't believe me, I'm just like, you know,
There you go. So there we go. Please solve them. Please solve them. I need to contact, I guess,
the text now. Have the IP traced and stuff like that. So yeah. Yep, yep, yep, yep. I mean,
it's pretty sick. Oh, here, there's going to keep going. I'm just going to, I'm just going to,
oh, hold on one second. Is it, I'm not exposed. You don't expose shit, dirty FAG. Then it says,
This is your future. I don't know what it is the po. Oh, it's a pogo stick
This is the future you're the pogo stick is your future. Well, I guess this person is the comfortable with putting stuff up there
Up there of their butt and that's in a vacuum. I have a vacuum is I like three vacuums this year
Yeah, it really is a hate crime. Yep
Really is a hate crime
Yeah, in real time we're watching hate crimes for interesting
Does anybody really?
I mean, I don't take it too seriously because it's just,
you know, recharge, I guess they can't help themselves.
Anyway, I've been looking for my vape
for like 20 minutes,
and so I'm gonna go look for it just a second,
but just, if it wants to come up,
I'm gonna put my link up, I'm gonna have some lemonade.
Here we go, text message is going this morning.
Yeah, I'm gonna actually on text now guys if you ever get these text now things. They do have a page
They will they will investigate these yeah, they will
stick filthy fag
Enjoy the lawnmower the Pogosic fifth stage is your boss. So this is the fifth stage and saying oh
No one watches or so. He's watching. He's watching
The fifth stage is such a little bitch. But first of all, he has like a thousand accounts. I mean
He liked Pogo sticks up his butt and I have a porno that he sent me of him doing that
He puts a condom on it and then he sits on it
And then he bounces around with it. I have the I have the video if you want to see it
I can't show it on YouTube. Obviously you're gonna have to contact me in private
I'll actually sell sell it
Yeah, one for the link and two for the stink, yep.
So I'm gonna put the link up
and I'm gonna hide myself
because I'm gonna be looking for my vape once.
I can't fit here, here, there you go.
I'm gonna invite you.
I'll actually show you how terrible my AI is.
You know, it's like I have no talent
in putting anything together or anything like that.
So I just want you to just see how terrible I am.
So here you go, enjoy this.
PIXEL GOSPENETHEL LIKE IT'S ALL TOO SOON
I think I'm not sure but um, yeah, I just want to say fifth stage
They still been calling you you think you still watch his name or you think there's someone else now
He's using the picture
He's using the pictures his profile photo that he's sending me so it's the same person
It's like this black lady that looks like I don't know her name is lucky Luciano or something like that
I don't look you know looks like Ruby Jimmy's family and stuff
If you like, you know, they're all taking a bunch of yeah, it's not the redone of each audio
It's the J-dog audio, but it's okay. J-dog so cute that he makes up for it. It's fine
The buy a bike my mic messed up. Hold on. It might be on the floor home. You guys hear me, okay?
You're my microphone is fine
Yeah, is my microphone messed up minus, okay? Well, I'll I'll mute one second make sure to fix it
There's an echo. I think it's on J-Dogs. I'm not sure. I thought it was him, but let me see if I can fix mine
I mean I've turned mine half down and
Do echo cancellation?
Is that better? Can you hear me now?
Is it too loud?
Okay, how's that don't try better
You can't hear me. Okay. Hello. Mm-hmm. You hear me? Okay. Oh, do you hear me? Okay? I turn my microphone down a little bit
I don't know it was like it was just a it was kind of like it's a little too dumb in there like
Hard to talk to like retarded people sometimes, you know
They're all retarded and it's like a retarded people are like making fun of you. It's like a little bit confusing
So I don't know I should make fun of them more. Hey look, so I have this thing called it's a boutique. It's a really good vape
Look at this vape. It's called boutique
Let's see what happens when I think it says
Pink haze so it has three different kinds of weed in it. See it's pretty good, huh?
Yeah, low battery is not banned
Well, I don't see the battery because I have them blocked personally, but they're not they're not um, they're not banned
I don't think
But if the battery would like to apologize to me, let me know if he does, and I'll unblock him
in person. But otherwise, he probably said something that was pretty offensive. And
that's the only reason I will usually block people when they talk about me or their chance in a bad
way. So I'll tell you who I blocked exactly too. Let me see if I can go to Google Contacts and see.
That's what I do because I don't like to see it like sometimes there's like a lot of stuff going on the screen
It was like, you know, I mean, I have a really tough skin about a lot of this
But you know, I just don't like to
Have to see it all the time but I'll tell you
Okay, my block list says
My block list I am person count his bathory the Kate show. Okay, I'll block Kate. Hold on a second
Not nags nacho mama low battery smoke detector all unbanned just to see what they're saying
I have a crumb and a czar
Beep beep
Beep you said I'm not bad. I'll block them. Hey BKG. Miffia. Miffia. It was gamble
Okay, I'm blocking it. Okay, William firearms on block William firearms
Devil eyes
I are unblocked, I was just, I was unblocked everybody.
Jenny girl, Jen Jen, Allie, oh my God,
I'm not blocking that person, no one.
He man is blocked.
Oh my God, there's a lot of people blocked actually.
Hannah, lovely lady.
Chetta Bob, Chrissy the Wolf, Viva La Terri Davis, Blacker RG, The Mike Hall Comedy Show,
He-Man She-Ra, Allied Master Computer, IRL Legends, Joseph Whelan, VKG Mafia, Ikram Nazar,
and then The Nacho Mama, Not Next, Countess Bathory. I am personally everyone a chance.
Again, even though I know I'll be re-blocking them. There we go. I just blocked like a lot of people.
Wow, I can't hit that baby anymore because it will knock me out. Hey, the microphone is good
You keep your camera. You're just gonna hurt your feelings again. Oh, you better not
But why are you doing talking about like, you know a personal thing? I mean, it's like mind your business low battery
I mean, it's like, you know what? You know what the low battery smoke detector does it goes?
Beep, beep, every two minutes
It's like a little annoying, like a little sound, right?
And you know, it's the sign of like a single woman sometimes
because women will learn how to block out that sound.
And it will just be like everybody like,
do you know that you have a low battery smoke detector?
And they're like, I didn't know that.
Everyone's unblocked.
Flipside is unblocked.
You're a mod.
I don't know, I don't think you ever unblocked.
Yeah, you're good, yeah.
Yeah.
I don't know. I was trying to be funny last night in like Sam. I actually had a fun night
last night in Sam Ants chat, but then this morning, not so much fun. It was just because
last night it wasn't, I just wasn't like spooking, ganging up on our attacks, you know, called
dirty and all these names before I even got to get to speak. I was able to like speak
and like dance and stuff like that. I told Alex, the Alex Siemens story and all those
kinds of stuff. Okay, anyway.
There was no semen, the whole thing was, it was never done, nothing, thank God, thank God, I didn't like, you know, bank my semen, you know, I mean, thank God.
I'll just say that, you know, please have sex or have a baby with that AI person she showed or whatever, okay, jeez.
I mean, that was called dodging a bullet, imagine, I mean, it's like, I would have created a monster, I don't know, I mean, I'm not like, my genes are good, but it's like, I just don't know, I just don't know, okay, anyway.
Oh gosh, okay. Um, yeah, I don't want to get any trouble
Put down the tape, um, okay
Well, I don't know it's time for coffee or something like I have a lemonade from last night this
Client a tarot client and she actually gave I get for the channel
She might show up and you know, I might I've been doing readings for people
And I've had people come over like a back again and again, so and so last night she sent me like there's some really amazing dinner
They're like like a filet mignon tacos
fish tacos
like the tuna
You know the raw tuna kind of stuff. It was like she door dashed to me last night. So it was really nice
And my Russian friend I talked to her and she like wants to like
Be on the show. I think
Within a couple days. I don't know. Yeah, I think I said this weekend because you know, she and I a bit like
She knows me with the cats and stuff like that like we spend so much time together
We used to hung out for so much time
And we love the cat then we just sit here cuddling the cat like all the time when she's here and it's so much fun
Yeah
But yeah, I haven't seen her for a while because she lives a little bit far away right now
But I think she wants to be on the show and there's other Russian person
It's just beautiful Russian girl like I've done readings for
Once to be on the show and then she introduced me to somebody else and that I've been doing readings for that
That's I got to talk of so wow, so I'm pretty lucky. I'm getting I am getting business
during tarot like even if I'm not doing on my show that much, but you know
Well a few cards for right now
This is interesting that well this one says storm I guess like walking through a storm like we're making it through storms
You have to crown right?
And then say we all but it's kind of like the spiritual crown
that will kind of like
Protect us in life. This one says every
Hurricane comes to an end. Yeah, so this is number 64 or two. There we go, but it's like, you know
Hold on to your, hold on to your head, you know, and I will carry you through like, you know
Anything that you need to get through in this life pretty much now we can figure out
um
We have the throne, okay
Sorry, I think there we go. We have the throne. Here you go
Yeah, yeah, if I let me on talk and I still have it I still have it
And it says your potential is endless. Okay, again, there's like a real royalty
vibe
Coming through like without even like, you know, no matter how high high class low class if you remember as like spiritual beings
It's like we are like royalty in the universe no matter what we are with this one says dragons to slay them all
Guess slay all the dragons. Okay, whatever those are in your life. These are these difficult circumstances or
temporary setbacks or or enemies or you know, but you know, remember to all the enemies are like basically
internal and a lot of times if you can slay these internal enemies that you can kind of like the external enemies
It's like at the both so below
This is a tower car, but it's not a bad tower car
It says unplug it and relax for a spell and this is like she's not she sits upside down
It's almost like a hangman. There's almost like a surrender or it's like, you know
Do something else like looks from a different perspective and just so long it's stuck in a rut that whatever you're doing like, you know do different
things to
experiment with life be creative and
And no matter what other people say about it,
cause you might share, you might not.
Like I share like a lot of my work
because it's like basically I like to archive it,
like I'm putting it on channels and stuff.
But, and people, some people like it
and some people don't, you know, it's like,
and so why is your main band?
I don't know, they're like over a hundred.
Is that me in that picture?
I hope not.
I don't know, give me your account
and I can look into it later,
but there's like a hundred band accounts
and so it's hard to like just go through.
Right now, you know, if you send a cash up, I'll do it faster, but, um, anyway, it's IBL.
Uh-huh.
That's IBL.
Okay.
Well, that's what it said.
You posted a flattering...
Oh, okay.
Oh, the picture.
You posted a flattering picture of me.
Okay.
I don't know about that.
Um, IBL, no.
Yeah, it looks like my ball. I have a bald um photo that I like I like I really do like it though
I mean, it's like I made this ball photo of myself. I like pretty good at it
I don't know if I can have it handy, but let me see maybe I do
I don't know I try to make Kate a piece of offering. I don't think she accepted it
You know she and now I get to I mean I had her block so I couldn't see her response to it
The receiver but everyone else did I guess oh here's a picture of jail. I was looking for
Yeah, oh my bald photo. I don't know
Here I should Joe's bald photo instead. I've done this one six are disturbing. Yeah
Yeah, okay, I have like my a few more days for this like premium stream yard
So if anyone wants me to do I can do like AI images real quick if you have ideas for like AI image
I can make that I can show you like
like
Since it's like a new account, I mean, I don't have that many.
I just had these two.
I just did.
There's this one space journey here, but I don't know.
But yeah, it won't show.
I don't know.
Black women in outer space or something.
She must work for NASA.
People are more scared of bald people than long-haired people.
I know, but the pictures they make of me
I have the long hair but they make me bald like all on top and I'm not at all like I'm not like at all like I have such thick luxurious hair I think my anything not receding hairline I've always had these things it's not receding I can pull it back I mean I always said this is where I horns used to be it's like there's just like a little little I see it looks like horns right kind of I don't know
If I didn't ban all people wouldn't be mad at me. Well, I don't know. I don't have them
I mean, it's like I have a lot of horrible things said about me and like a lot of doxing on this on these banned accounts
And so I'm not sure I should just like, you know, I'm ban all of them, you know, willy-nilly
You know, a lot of them are like this ages accounts. I don't like him
But I've seen I've seen that guy. He's cute
But yeah, I would probably have sex with him
Which is different when someone's like Brandon Hughes harassing it. Yeah, I know exactly is different and now I have said, you know
Look over my shoulder. Yeah
I mean, I've got Alexandra Brandon Q after me. Thank God I'm brother in X because I mean it's like imagine
I had all three after me. Oh my god
No, I don't know. I don't know. I mean
Um, yeah, I don't know. I'm still still alive here. Um, let's watch, uh, let's watch that stoner scribe
I don't think he minds me playing this, but yeah, like, you know, make sure you like check out his channel stoner scribe and
You know, he does like a lot of these really funny like skits and stuff like acting
He does ally is a really good Alex. So, um
I want to go through this ski mask handy phase and watch maybe one or two of these videos
every show or something until we get through that saga.
Let me see, okay, hold on a second, oh, look who's here, one second, I'm sorry, here you
go, Mason!
Sike!
Hi, what's up?
Hey, Sike, we're still cool, man.
Of course, we're always cool.
It's like I came back and see you
You can't make to see me. Thank you
Wow
You look at Mason someone in the chat said you're kind of cute
You are you are a very good-looking guy
Yeah, oh, oh, see you got a shy. Yeah, a little shy. Okay. Well, it's okay. Hey look at those nice drums
Are those your drums man? Are you those your drums or um, are those um, the drums you want? Oh, they are your drums. Wow
I'm so happy. There was a time when Mason didn't have his drum set, and then then then someone broke his last drum set
Some jerk broke his last drum set, but Mason has procured in third drum set
I remember he sold the first one for for groceries, you know
but um
You know, I think you must I think you got that sorted out and then someone broke his second. Sorry second. Yeah
Yeah, that's true
I'm sorry. I mean, I said, yeah, um, it's really sad, you know, but I'm just really happy that you have your drum set
Yeah, so I think so you're happy that I got him back. I got my drum set that yeah
Where they fit you didn't fix or you got a new new drum set or something like that
I had to get a whole another one site because other one somebody destroyed remember. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
The guy it was like it was like some guy or mom knew or some yeah some uh, yeah, and he broke them when he got mad or something
Yeah, I was my mom's so called friend, but then he turned on her and they started doing some bad stuff
Yeah, oh my gosh. That's just a pretty jerk. I mean, it's like how terrible I'm glad he's out of your life
My mom thought he was a friend, but he turned he wasn't at the end though
Yeah, I hate when that happens. I'll talk about towards the end. It's like yeah. Yeah, it's so you know
It's so relatable Mason, you know that something that happens sometimes
You know where it's like, you know someone that you really care for will just turn on you for no reason and then like
You know blame you for it and something like that, which is like, you know
What's pretty much happened to me in this situation, but anyway
And then it was Christians around. I've never seen Christians. Sometimes you don't think that guy is funny. Okay. Well Mason
Do you have you ever seen stoner's crap? Oh, I don't know if you you um, oh
What's going on tell me more about what's going on? Oh, what do you mean? It's like what's going on?
Like how are you like everything good in your life? You've been saying out of trouble
You haven't been trespassing at churches or anything
No, I've been I've been doing what I was supposed to do like I don't do anything wrong
Okay, good good. Yeah, I know you're a good guy and it's like, you know
So like you got me a Jar Jar Big shirt
Your jar jar being sure you heard that your song you like you're so you're in that song
You know, I said there's several versions of that song now and so that's I think that song is gonna be a hit
It's just it's your weird song because one time in a beat is chat
Um, thing that just started mocking Sam-an and saying,
you're weird, you're weird, you're weird, you're weird.
That's why it's called, that's why it's like, you're weird.
But it's also kind of something that is what it says,
that you're weird, I don't know.
You're, I don't know.
So yeah, but you're in the song too because he didn't it's like I would like a jar jar. I would like a jar jar big shirt
I'm gonna be looking out for one if I went on team it
But you have to give me your address I guess because or you know, I'll have to like, you know
I'll have to point it to you and give you you know, you give me the money for are you still are you still mad right now?
It's like from what happened to you before with that person that was making you mad like
I'm mad when I know I was yelling last night shit. I mean it's like I feel bad
Oh, I get like so angry sometimes and like, you know, oh my I don't even remember like
What made you yell and stuff like that I got mad last night because I was trying to talk
and explained something on a show last night
and they wouldn't let me talk.
They literally, I can't, they wouldn't let me talk.
And so then I kept asking Cash App.
I was gonna pay for like $5, so I could have one minute to talk and she and it wouldn't give the cash
Or no, no state terms last night
And I was like say turn as a cash out cash. I was I was gonna send $5 for one minute of
uninterrupted so I could tell my story about summer and it wouldn't let me and
And then I did which is another chat and they wouldn't let me and then so I did my own chat
And I was really mad by that point because I just felt like I
I was trying to let you, like, pay to speak to them.
Oh, it's like, it was a thing that happened with Alexandria, right?
Like, she did something that made you mad and stuff?
Well, that too.
I mean, she, like, she's going too far.
Maybe it's like threatening me and saying that she's gonna try to make my life like a living hell and stuff like that
But I don't know maybe she didn't mean it or maybe she was I don't know my words in her mouth
I'm just trying to like cease fire and
But it's just like so it's just got so scary and it's like how she really feels and stuff
I mean, it's like not like, you know
Like they don't show up. She'll be arrested or anything. I don't know. I'm not doing anything legal against her
But it's like I have to you know
So, uh, stand up for the privacy of certain things, and it's like, she's going too far
with what she shared.
I asked her nicely to take it down, and she's like, you know, she doubled down and stuff
like that.
Dogs are my family, all kinds of stuff, so it's not funny anymore.
Yeah.
I can understand that.
Thank you.
Yep.
So, what day is it?
It's Saturday?
Yeah, I don't know. It's like a lazy Saturday kind of what do you up to today?
It's just Saturday morning?
Yeah.
I'm just at home right now like yeah
Well, you look really good. Oh, yeah, you know watch watch
Some funny thing we see
I'm gonna share something on we see I'm gonna share share something I like this guy
Let's see
Are you still tired? It's like cuz you're still laying down
Am I still that I just smoked a fucking couple hits of his vape and it's pretty powerful and
Yeah, okay, let's see here. Let's see this this little here. It's like this is stoner scribe everybody
Subscribers stoner scribe to you home. I've never heard of that
Yeah, well, you're back to see it
To get ready. Oh, it's here. Oh, jade. I was back here a lot. So, yeah
Okay, sorry
That's a snake in the background like behind you yo
Like II what's up?
Not much here. Talk to Mason first. Yeah, Mason. What's up, bro?
They tell you so remember me. Yeah, I remember you Mason. How you been?
I've been okay. Yeah, I remember everything that is and all that they used to come that he's come in here
Yeah, he's still there. I see him in chat
Thing that is yeah
Okay
Yeah, I seen him in the chat. I think yesterday or maybe even earlier today. I'm not sure but I know it was
Within the last 24 hours
Yeah, he used to tease me about the jar jar binks like shirts and stuff like that.
Oh, yeah, don't let them get to you. Don't let them bother you.
Don't let them get to me, Jato?
No, don't let them bother you. Don't let them bother you at all.
Yeah, and so if they bother you or anything like that, just ignore them.
Okay.
Yeah, that's what I do.
So you've been okay, Jato?
Yeah.
How about you, Mason, just been drumming away?
Yeah, I've been drumming sometimes like, yeah
Hell yeah
J-Dog I could play sometimes
Sometimes that's what's up
No, you got clip yeah, okay. I'm on mute
what you see today, consider donating down below. Oh, you see it? Oh, is it coming up? Yeah, yeah.
A little bit helps the channel grow. Thank you so much. Enjoy. This should be good. Let me,
let me take another look at this email that I'm sending just to make sure that it's threatening
garbage, dumpster fire, white supremacist, racist, neo-nazi, criminal stalker gang, and
channel the outcast owls.
I am disgusted by your use of a celebrity impersonator whose name will not be mentioned
in this email because it is not even worth my mentioning.
Come at me by inappropriately using my full legal name in your parody and insulting my
reckless abandon. It is completely inappropriate for you to use my legal name in your videos.
I would never do that. Can't imagine doing the same thing. At this point, you are guilty of
numerous legally actionable offenses and I will be getting my attorney to look into your organization.
This is still inscribed. I don't know Johnny. Give me a peace sign a
Peace sign. Okay. Hello. This is for some doing
No, no who that is
Oh, it's Nick. Okay. Yeah, it's Tony Soprano. Oh, oh my god. Oh
Nick Johansson, oh my god
No, you're not Nick Johansson. You're not thought you're not that guy who skates
Drugs spice. What is that?
You're supposed to be the guy from Scarface
No, no, J-Dog is not from Scarface not at all. I'll tell you about the guy that's on here the Tony guy. Oh
Yeah, Tony's no Tony Soprano. He's supposed to I think he's like from
What do you call what's that show?
So Soprano's not now. Yeah
Oh, I was thinking of the guy from Scarface. That's right Robert Robert De Niro or no someone Al Pacino
Yeah, yeah, no, no. He's this guy's
This Nick Johansson guy. He's like mentally retarded
So, you know, and he likes to just do a lot of he's on camera
Or something like that
No, he's like
he lacks the
Three of us on panel have so Nick. Well, what he left a lot of
Look at what?
Nick is
Retarded like a hundred percent retarded, right Nick
Shake your head for yes. Shake your head for no
Yeah, he's slow, he's retarded
So he does one time I remember him let's get a tire
Um, he just kept flipping it over and over and over.
Yeah.
He's, he's slow.
You'll notice him.
He just wants to come on camera and just do things in front of the camera.
He's like a dancing monkey.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Uh, they talk about that.
That's what I'm asking.
Yeah.
Um, he go, he, oh, he's mad, look at Nick's mad, like, what's he gonna do?
Wasn't it like still here? Yeah, it's like he's just chillin
What is he doing? I mean the Tony guy
Like he look what he got look what Nick's got
No, he just no you got a rewinded dude he had he had to he he hella put something up on your your thing, bro
He did have it something on your
What is that J dog? What is he doing?
Jaydo, Jaydo, are you still there?
Yes, Nick.
Sorry.
Where's Jaydo?
Yeah, we're gonna watch more of this here.
Okay, yeah, that's all right, that's all right.
What a disgusting video that celebrity impersonator made of me.
I can let a lot of things slide off my back.
I can let Schema's candy call me the N word once or twice.
I can forgive controller for saying that I have HIV
when I don't, but what I will not let roll off my back
is my faith in Jesus Christ.
I am more motivated now than ever
to everyone that I can.
It's so refreshing spending time with you.
I know that when I'm in your presence,
I am in the presence of a godly, refined woman
with a love and appreciation of Jesus Christ and the Bible.
Oh yeah, Alex.
You know that this is the godliest house
in Wall of Staten Island.
The fucking Vatican is the holy end of this house.
I'm facing a hideous attack on my faith right now, and I don't really care to spend any
time with people that don't agree with the Bible.
I know that sounds terrible, but that's where I am at.
Oh yeah, you know I've never believed in anything other than the Bible.
I've always been a Christian and I've never been any other religion.
There is a hideous, dangerous world out there for Christians.
The Roman Empire has never left us, but God will smite the wicked and plunge them into the fiery pit.
The celebrity impersonator who mocked my faith will probably get struck by lightning.
Yeah, don't fuck with the man upstairs!
I need the company of godly people like you, not like that pig Amber.
Oh, your Amber is fucking pathetic. Amber HHHH. She is a fucking disgusted bitch.
They don't make fat fucking nails if it's rip a hole in a fucking toilet paper.
Did you hear that she and her fiance now have active warrants?
She is a terrible human being and an even worse mother.
What kind of mother would use drugs in the same kind of thing we'd use to fucking drive their son?
that fucking disgusting Amber.
Why did she had an accident involving her king?
You know how fucked up that would be?
I am so glad I was never her friend.
I am so glad that I never messaged her on Instagram
or did any live panels with her
or in any way supported her channel with my channel.
She's really not the kind of person
that won't enter through the gates of heaven.
You've got such a brilliant mind on your shoulders controller and I want you to know that I did find a passage
while I was reading the Bible that I think really applies to you specifically
starting in Exodus
ye shall not afflict any widow or fatherless child.
If thou afflict them in any way wise,
and they cry at all unto me, I will surely hear their cry.
And my wrath shall wax hot, and I will kill you with the sword,
and your wives will be widows, and your children fatherless."
Woo!
I like this part of the Bible.
It's so dramatic.
It's so, so violent.
Controla.
What?
What's going on?
There is no way you should be sleeping whenever there's somebody reading the Bible.
That is sacrilege.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to fall asleep.
I think I stayed up late last night watching you play gaming with Chad.
It's not called gaming with chat.
It's called live gaming.
Somebody who watches me a little too closely
called it gaming with chat.
I only have cooking with chat.
Doesn't live gaming sound better anyways?
It captures all of the excitement
of watching a 44-year-old woman play Tetris.
Well, Alex, I know how much you love the Bible, and it would be easy to convince me of how great the Bible is because I am, of course, a deeply devout Christian woman.
Maybe it would be more effective if you were to talk to somebody that didn't have the same love of Jesus that I do.
Interesting.
I'm already devoted to Jesus. You want to know the reason why I took Eli out of public school?
It's because one of the first things that you see when you walk into a school
is an lgbt, a plus, plus, plus, negative, whatever flag.
Right at the end of front.
There's no American flag.
I want to replace the LGBT flag with a cross.
I'd rather shove going down my daughter's throat rather than trains this.
In fact, in fact...
I would be totally okay with her being a sex worker and being a prostitute if she wanted to
in the future, but I don't want transness in any way, afflicting my daughter. I could bring
the Word of God to someone that doesn't have the passion for Jesus Christ burning in their heart.
That would be the true test of my abilities in the Word of the Bible.
I will find the most godless, disgusting harlot there is, and converter to Christianity.
You'll be just like Christopher Lambez!
bringing the light of Jesus into the new world.
You'll do all kinds of good things just like him.
It might be a bit of a long walk,
but it's a good thing that I got myself
this Fiji bottled water to keep me refreshed.
I absolutely love Fiji.
It is my favorite bottled water.
I just love Fiji. I'll totally pay $3 at the gas station for it.
I can afford it after all the nicotine that I quit.
Hey, controller, would you like to hear about how much I love Fiji bottled water?
I am so glad that I blocked you on Instagram.
Hello, Jennifer. Oh, my God!
Alex, Alex, what are you doing in my house?
I am here to grant you the greatest favor
that anyone has ever given you.
How did you even get in?
I stuck it through the window.
Do not change the subject.
I am here because I am ready to introduce you
to the word of God.
At this fucking time of night?
Sit and never rest Jennifer and based on all the actions that you've taken recently on this channel
I am convinced that the devil has placed a seed of evil inside your mind
And now it's grown to such a degree that it is
Uncontrolled and it is my responsibility as a woman of God to take that evil plant that has grown in your mind and
tear it out of the ground
This will be the true test of all my powers in the Word of God, and I needed to find the
most reprehensible, almost completely irredeemable parent there is to give myself a challenge.
Did you really?
You only break into my house just to insult me?
You are such a bitch.
Don't be so haughty as to think that there aren't words in the Bible that can't apply
to you.
For instance, oh, yes, there was a line in Matthew 7.15 that I think applied to me.
Beware of false prophets who come to you in sheep's clothing, but inward, I think I highlighted
the wrong part of the Bible.
Excuse me, just one moment.
Ah, here we go.
They profess that they know God, but in works they deny him being
abominable and just so who is
Highlighting my butt. I don't know who my team is highlighting my Bible
But I can assure you that they're gonna be fired Alex. You've been having a hard on for me since
2019 it's time to stop now. I don't think you're gonna be the person
that is going to turn me to God. Who is better to bring you under the wing of Christianity
other than I? Alexandra Melody Mayers. I have escaped the adult film industry because of Christianity.
You're looking at a woman whose life was saved by accepting Christ as her Lord and Savior. In fact,
it was a woman by the name of Shelley LeVon who introduced me to Christianity and I am very certain.
That when she is up there in heaven that she looks down at me and everything I support and everything that I do on YouTube
And she would be proud. I really think you should just leave
Where are your KKK hoods Jennifer?
Excuse me
You are one of the worst white supremacists I've ever seen Jennifer
I know that you have KKK hoods hiding somewhere in this house. I
Checked all your closets and I couldn't find them, but where are they?
Get the hell out of my house!
I couldn't expect a racist to give me any hospitality,
so that's no problem.
I can see myself out of your house.
You have a good day, Miss Racist Whites of Pravacist.
It's time for me to get ready for my daily reading.
Daily reading.
Let me open my account.
A credit card that was taken out of my name
in Yuma, Arizona?
How do they even get access to my legal records this is going to destroy everything this is going to be destroy my perfect image of everything oh
God why have you forsaken me?
Why have you brought these elements into my life to cause me destruction?
haven't I been your soldier your word the soldier of your word your champion
my enemies are swarming around me because of
Yes, that's what it is. Jealousy.
They are sinners in the hands of an angry God, and they want to taunt and humiliate me and destroy me for being a preacher of the Word of God.
Everybody is jealous of my fabulous lifestyle as a former porn actress with an IMDb page that a total of 50 people have ever seen they deserve to suffer.
And I hope they suffer.
If you liked what you see today, leave a like leave a comment down below and of course subscribe to stoner scribe
Thank you so much until next time
It may take a while to get there, but it's a good thing that I brought myself some bg bottle
What's up guys, how are you? I'm sorry. I don't have people but I mean I have to go and fix my mod
I think there's some people that aren't model here, but yeah, so
What's up? What's up, Mace? What is he doing? He's uh
If he's Tony Soprano
Yeah, but why is he doing all that? It's like I don't understand
I don't really understand either a long second. You can put us on the side here
site
Yeah, I know that jj said or j what his name j dog said that uh, he has like uh,
You know problems, but yeah, I don't know
Well, describe what he's doing to me. I'm not looking right now. No, it's like I have mental problems too, though
You know this. I mean, it's kind of similar
My hallucinating is he like is he in a ball? Is he bald and he's like, but what is he doing?
I can't figure out what he's doing. I can't focus on it. I just like yeah, I believe he's bald
I think he's trying. I think he's bald or something like that. It's like, yeah
Hey psyche
But yeah, what is he doing?
Like why does he have a base? Why does he have a baseball bet though for like? What is that for like?
Why would he have baseball?
Maybe he played baseball. Oh, it's he's a grandpa
That makes no sense. No, it's like if he wants to play baseball, he's supposed to be outside though. I know
Maybe he's like, I don't know maybe he plays on the indoor league
You get to spend time with your site. Do you get to spend time with your family or anything like that or no?
Not recently
See how that why is he of that hat? I don't know. See maybe the grandfather
So you see by yourself site with your cats and that's it. Yeah
How are you what are you up to? Oh, I'm just at home. So like I said, are you bored?
Huh? Are you bored a little bit?
Is Nick still on the screen it's like you, huh?
Nick hear you Nick. Can you talk to Mason? It's like they talking
Yeah, I don't hear anything
Nick it's like what's going on. Why's why's it wasn't a safety? Oh, but try talking to see if he reacts to you
Don't see if he reacts like talk to him. I don't know what you want me to do. Say
Nick are you?
Do you sign language?
Nick wave if you can hear me
Do you wave?
No
Maybe he's deaf
It's like hold on give me a minute
Sike
Yes
What are you doing sleeping?
Oh, where did Nick go? Oh my gosh
It's like you weren't saying anything right?
I wasn't you were either. Where were you? I'm sorry though. Huh? Oh, well, I don't know. I'm like, uh, I fall asleep
It's like you fell asleep
No, I'm wide awake. It's like all right. Did you saw you saw did you say you fall fell asleep?
Well, I can make was supposed to be entertaining everybody and then like disappeared
Was that why you fell asleep though, or what do you mean? Yes?
Well, I thought you had me though. Like, you know what I'm saying
Are you okay? It's like you're just tired like I asked you I told you you're tired before, right?
Yeah, I just smoke weed. I don't know
I see I'll be back. I'm sorry guys. Okay, I know I suck right now and it probably just
You want me to come back later? It's like
I love you guys, yeah.
Mois.
Love you Mason.
Yeah.
I love you.
Okay.
We'll talk to you soon, okay?
I'll talk to you, yeah, later.